<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>New South Wales</region><office>NSWRO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDN11003</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-18T17:10:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T04:10:00+11:00</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-18T17:10:31Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-19T17:10:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T00:00:00+11:00</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-21T23:59:59+11:00</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T05:05:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T16:05:00+11:00</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSM</service><sub-service>FCW</sub-service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="NSW_FA001" description="New South Wales" type="region"><warning-summary type="marine_forecast" start-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z">Strong Wind Warning for Saturday for Batemans Coast and Eden Coast</warning-summary><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z"><warning-summary type="marine_forecast" start-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T04:10:31+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T17:10:31Z">Strong Wind Warning for Saturday for Batemans Coast and Eden Coast</warning-summary><text type="synoptic_situation">A high pressure system in the Bight is extending a ridge into New South Wale in the wake of a cold front. This high is expected to maintain a ridge over coastal parts for the next few days as it drifts slowly east, likely reaching the Tasman Sea early in the new week. As a result, coastal winds should remain generally southerly through this period.</text><text type="preamble">Wind gusts can be 40 percent stronger than the averages given here, and maximum waves may be up to twice the height.</text><text type="warning_summary_footer">Details of warnings are available on the Bureau's website www.bom.gov.au, by telephone 1300-659-218* or through some TV and radio broadcasts.</text><text type="product_footer">* Calls to 1300 numbers cost around 27.5c incl. GST, higher from mobiles or public phones.</text><text type="postamble">Check the latest Coastal Waters Forecasts for information on wind, wave and weather conditions for neighbouring coastal zones.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="NSW_MW005" description="Hunter Coast: Seal Rocks to Broken Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="NSW_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching 20 knots offshore in the morning, turning south to southeasterly in the afternoon and evening. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southeasterly around 1 metre, tending southerly 1.5 to 2.5 metres during the day. Swell: East to northeasterly around 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. Caution: Large and powerful surf conditions in the afternoon and evening are expected to be hazardous for coastal activities such as crossing bars by boat and rock fishing.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching 20 knots offshore in the evening. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southerly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 70% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots turning southerly 15 to 20 knots during the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore. Swell: Southerly 2 metres, tending southeasterly 1.5 to 2 metres during the morning. Swell: Easterly around 1 metre. Weather: Cloudy. 60% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="NSW_MW004" description="Sydney Coast: Broken Bay to Port Hacking" type="coast" parent-aac="NSW_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 20 knots, turning south to southeasterly in the afternoon and evening Seas: 1 to 2 metres. Swell: Southerly 1 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the afternoon and evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. Caution: Large and powerful surf conditions in the afternoon and evening are expected to be hazardous for coastal activities such as crossing bars by boat and rock fishing.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southerly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 70% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southerly 15 to 20 knots during the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon or evening. Swell: Southerly 2 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 60% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="NSW_MW003" description="Illawarra Coast: Port Hacking to Ulladulla" type="coast" parent-aac="NSW_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 20 knots, reaching 25 knots south of Port Kembla in the morning, turning south to southeasterly in the afternoon and evening. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: Southerly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the day. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers late this afternoon and evening. Caution: Large and powerful surf conditions in the afternoon and evening are expected to be hazardous for coastal activities such as crossing bars by boat and rock fishing.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 20 knots turning southeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the morning. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southerly 2 to 3 metres, increasing to 4 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 70% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots turning southerly 15 to 20 knots during the morning. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southeasterly 1.5 to 2 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
