<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>Queensland</region><office>QLDRO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDQ10700</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-18T18:30:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T04:30:00+10:00</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-18T18:30:16Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-28T18:30:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T04:30:16+10:00</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-25T23:59:59+10:00</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T06:30:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T16:30:00+10:00</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSP</service><sub-service>FST</sub-service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="QLD_FA001" description="Queensland" type="region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T04:30:16+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T04:30:16+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:16Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:16Z"><text type="synoptic_situation">A tropical low over the northwest Coral Sea is expected to move eastwards away from the Queensland coast over the next few days. The monsoon flow over the far north of the state will continue to weaken as the monsoon burst also moves eastwards into the Coral Sea. An inland surface trough is expected to move into the far southeast of the state during today with a coastal trough moving north through far southeast Queensland. The inland surface trough will then move slowly westwards from Sunday. A series of upper troughs will move across the south of the state over the next few days.</text><text type="warning_summary_footer">For latest warnings go to www.bom.gov.au, subscribe to RSS feeds, call 1300-659-219* or listen for warnings on relevant TV and radio broadcasts.</text><text type="product_footer">* Calls to 1300 numbers cost around 27.5c incl. GST, higher from mobiles or public phones.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">A high to very high chance of showers and storms over the northern Peninsula with some heavy falls possible in thunderstorms. A medium to high chance of showers and storms about the southeast, and some storms may be severe. A slight to medium chance of showers and possible storms about the tropical interior.Fine and mostly sunny in the west, Central West and southern interior. Light to moderate south to southeasterly winds, tending fresh west to northwesterly over the far north.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">The monsoon flow will continue to weaken over far northern Queensland the low in Coral Sea moves further away from the Queensland coast. The coastal surface trough will shift further north along the Wide Bay and Capricornia coast as the inland trough starts to move slowly westwards. Meanwhile, a high near Tasmania will extend a firm ridge along the southern and central east Queensland coast. A slight to medium chance of showers and thunderstorms anywhere near and east of the inland trough, more likely over the far northern Peninsula. Fine and mostly sunny for western Queensland.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">A high over the Tasman Sea will continue to extend a ridge along the Queensland coast while the inland trough becomes slow moving over the interior of the state. An upper level trough over the south will enhance the instability. A slight to medium chance of showers and storms near and northeast of the trough with storms more likely near the surface trough. Fine and mostly sunny for western Queensland.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">The inland trough will move slowly west with showers and storms possible near and east of the trough especially about the southern and central interior, and northern tropics, although generally more isolated as the upper atmosphere stabilises. Fine and mostly sunny southwest of the trough. The subtropical ridge along the southern Tasman Sea and southern parts of the country will continue to extend a ridge along the Queensland coast, with the onshore flow providing moisture for the chance of showers along the east coast.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="4" end-index="6" end-date-local="2016-03-25T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-26T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-22T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-25T14:00:00Z"><text type="outlook">The inland trough will move slowly west with showers and storms possible near and east of the trough especially about the southern and central interior, and northern tropics. Fine and mostly sunny southwest of the trough. The subtropical ridge along the southern Tasman Sea and southern parts of the country will continue to extend a ridge along the Queensland coast, with the onshore flow providing moisture for the chance of showers along the east coast.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
