<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>Queensland</region><office>QLDRO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDQ11292</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-18T18:45:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T04:45:00+10:00</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-18T18:46:18Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-19T18:45:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T00:00:00+10:00</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-21T23:59:59+10:00</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T05:50:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="EST">2016-03-19T15:50:00+10:00</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSM</service><sub-service>FCW</sub-service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="QLD_FA003" description="North Queensland" type="sub-region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T14:00:00Z"><text type="synoptic_situation">The monsoon trough lies from the north of Cape York Peninsula and over the northwest Coral Sea with a tropical low located on the trough well off the northeast Queensland coast. The low is expected to continue moving eastwards across the Coral Sea over the next few days. A weak ridge should gradually extend northwards along the east Queensland coast on Sunday and into early next week.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_FA001" description="Queensland" type="region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T04:46:19+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T04:46:19+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:46:19Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:46:19Z"><text type="preamble">Wind gusts can be 40 percent stronger than the averages given here, and maximum waves may be up to twice the height. Wind warnings are issued for today and tomorrow and describe the highest category of wind warning for that day.</text><text type="warning_summary_footer">For latest warnings go to www.bom.gov.au, subscribe to RSS feeds, call 1300-360-427* or listen for warnings on relevant TV and radio broadcasts.</text><text type="product_footer">* Calls to 1300 numbers cost around 27.5c incl. GST, higher from mobiles or public phones. Marine forecasts are also available on VHF and HF radio. View the radio schedule on www.bom.gov.au/marine</text><text type="postamble">Check the latest Coastal Waters Forecasts for information on wind, wave and weather conditions for neighbouring coastal zones.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW003" description="Torres Strait" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Westerly 15 to 20 knots, reaching up to 25 knots offshore east of Cape York in the morning. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres by early evening. Swell: Westerly 1 to 1.5 metres outside the reef. Weather: Cloudy. 90% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to northwesterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots offshore east of Cape York in the morning. Winds decreasing to about 10 knots in the early afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre, decreasing below 1 metre during the afternoon. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 70% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to northwesterly 10 to 15 knots decreasing to about 10 knots during the afternoon. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW004" description="Peninsula Coast: Sharp Point to Cape Melville" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northwest to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable about 10 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Easterly around 1 metre outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 70% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southeasterly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 0.5 metres. Swell: Southeasterly around 1 metre outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW005" description="Cooktown Coast: Cape Melville to Cape Tribulation" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots offshore in the morning. Winds turning southeasterly in the afternoon. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre around midday. Swell: Easterly 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to around 1 metre by early evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers north of Cooktown, 30% chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm during the morning and afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 10 to 15 knots turning southeasterly in the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: East to southeasterly around 1 metre outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm inshore in the afternoon and evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: East to southeasterly around 1 metre outside the reef, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm in the afternoon and evening.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW006" description="Cairns Coast: Cape Tribulation to Cardwell" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots offshore in the morning. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre later in the evening. Swell: Easterly below 1 metre. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly about 10 knots tending southeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the morning then decreasing to about 10 knots in the late evening. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: East to southeasterly 1 to 1.5 metres outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southeasterly 1 to 1.5 metres outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW007" description="Townsville Coast: Cardwell to Bowen" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwest to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: East to northeasterly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly about 10 knots increasing to 10 to 15 knots in the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Easterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Easterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres outside the reef. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW008" description="Mackay Coast: Bowen to St Lawrence" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly about 10 knots increasing to 10 to 15 knots early in the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: East to northeasterly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Easterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="QLD_MW015" description="Great Barrier Reef Offshore Waters" type="coast" parent-aac="QLD_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T19:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Easterly 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to around 1 metre during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots through the Capricorn Channel in the late evening. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: East to southeasterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres through the Capricorn Channel during the afternoon. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T14:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T14:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres through the Capricorn Channel. Swell: Southeasterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres through the Capricorn Channel. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
