<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>South Australia</region><office>SARO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDS11071</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-18T18:40:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="CDT">2016-03-19T05:10:00+10:30</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-18T18:41:54Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-19T18:40:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="CDT">2016-03-19T00:00:00+10:30</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="CDT">2016-03-21T23:59:59+10:30</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T05:20:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="CDT">2016-03-19T15:50:00+10:30</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSM</service><sub-service>FCW</sub-service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="SA_FA001" description="South Australia" type="region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:11:54+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-19T05:11:54+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:41:54Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:41:54Z"><text type="preamble">Wind gusts can be 40 percent stronger than the averages given here. Wind warnings are issued for today and tomorrow and describe the highest category of wind warning for that day.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW001" description="Far West Coast: WA-SA Border to Fowlers Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: Easterly 5 to 10 knots increasing to 10 to 15 knots in the early afternoon, 15 to 20 knots knots</p><p>inshore late afternoon and throughout in the evening. Seas: 0.5 to 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres</p><p>early evening. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower offshore.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeast to easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower from the late morning. The chance of a thunderstorm in the late afternoon and evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW002" description="Upper West Coast: Fowlers Bay to Elliston" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: East to southeasterly 5 to 10 knots tending southeast to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots in the early</p><p>afternoon then tending southeasterly in the evening. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to around 1 metre</p><p>during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower south of Streaky Bay.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeast to easterly 10 to 15 knots tending south to southeasterly in the early afternoon, increasing to southeasterly 15 to 20 knots from late afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 10 to 15 knots tending southeasterly during the afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres during the afternoon or evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW003" description="Lower West Coast: Elliston to Cape Carnot" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: South to southeasterly 5 to 10 knots, reaching 10 to 15 knots inshore during the afternoon. Seas:</p><p>Below 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly about 10 knots, becoming south to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the afternoon, becoming southeasterly in the evening and reaching 15 to 20 knots offshore. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres, decreasing to 2 metres by early evening. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW004" description="Central Coast" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: South to southwesterly 5 to 10 knots becoming east to southeasterly in the late evening. Seas: Below</p><p>1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly about 10 knots increasing to 10 to 15 knots early in the morning, becoming southeasterly 15 to 20 knots in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres, decreasing to 2 metres later in the evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower in the morning and early afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW008" description="South Central Coast" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: South to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots easing to 5 to 10 knots in the morning then becoming east to</p><p>southeasterly 10 to 15 knots mid afternoon. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, increasing to 15 to 20 knots from late afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres, decreasing to 2 metres later in the evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower west of Kangaroo Island in the morning.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW009" description="Upper South East Coast: Murray Mouth to Cape Jaffa" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots turning south to southeasterly in the morning and reaching 15 to 20</p><p>knots at times from late afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower in the morning and early afternoon.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeast to easterly 10 to 15 knots, turning south to southeasterly 15 to 20 knots in the afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable 5 to 10 knots during the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre, decreasing below 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres. Weather: Sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW010" description="Lower South East Coast: Cape Jaffa to SA-VIC Border" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: South to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching 15 to 20 knots south of Beachport in the early</p><p>morning, then tending south to southeasterly in the afternoon and evening. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing</p><p>to 0.5 to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeast to easterly 10 to 15 knots, tending south to southeasterly in the afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres early evening. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower south of Beachport.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots decreasing to 5 to 10 knots during the morning then increasing to 15 to 20 knots south of Port MacDonnell during the afternoon. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres south of Port MacDonnell during the evening. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Cloud clearing.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW005" description="Spencer Gulf" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable 5 to 10 knots early in the morning. Southerly</p><p>afternoon sea breezes 10 to 15 knots, reaching 15 to 20 knots north of Cowell to Wallaroo from late afternoon, tending southeasterly 10 to 15 knots late evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly 1 to 2 metres south of Cowell to Wallaroo. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southwest to southeasterly in the afternoon, then southeasterly around 15 knots in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres south of Cowell to Wallaroo. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower south of Port Neill to Port Victoria in the morning and early afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northeast to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable 5 to 10 knots during the day then becoming east to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots during the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres south of Cowell to Wallaroo. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW006" description="Gulf St Vincent" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: Southerly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable 5 to 10 knots early morning, tending southerly in the</p><p>afternoon and southeasterly in the evening. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: West to southwesterly below 0.5</p><p>metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southeast to southwesterly in the middle of the day then tending southeasterly around 15 knots in the evening. Seas: Below 1 metre, decreasing below 0.5 metres during the morning, then increasing to around 1 metre during the afternoon. Swell: Southeast to southwesterly below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to northeasterly 10 to 15 knots turning south to southeasterly during the day then tending east to southeasterly during the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southeast to southwesterly below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="SA_MW007" description="Investigator Strait" type="coast" parent-aac="SA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast"><p>Winds: Southerly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable 5 to 10 knots before dawn. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell:</p><p>West to southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres through the Backstairs Passage. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</p></text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots becoming southeast to northeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the afternoon, then becoming southeasterly 15 to 20 knots in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres in the evening. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres through the Backstairs Passage. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+10:30" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+10:30" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:30:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:30:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
