<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>Tasmania</region><office>TASRO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDT15123</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-18T23:00:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T10:00:00+11:00</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-18T23:01:33Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-19T23:00:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T00:00:00+11:00</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-21T23:59:59+11:00</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T06:15:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="EDT">2016-03-19T17:15:00+11:00</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSM</service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="TAS_FA001" description="Tasmania" type="region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T10:01:33+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T10:01:33+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T23:01:33Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-18T23:01:33Z"><text type="synoptic_situation">A low over the Tasman Sea will move away to the east today, as a high approaches from the west and extends a ridge over Tasmania. The high centre will slowly pass to the south of the state late on Sunday then move away to the southeast on Monday, directing an easterly flow over Tasmania.</text><text type="preamble">Wind gusts can be 40 percent stronger than the averages given here, and maximum waves may be up to twice the height. Wind warnings are issued for today and tomorrow and describe the highest category of wind warning for that day.</text><text type="warning_summary_footer">For latest warnings go to www.bom.gov.au, subscribe to RSS feeds, call 1300-659-216* or listen for warnings on relevant TV and radio broadcasts.</text><text type="product_footer">* Calls to 1300 numbers cost around 27.5c incl. GST, higher from mobiles or public phones. Marine forecasts are also available on VHF and HF radio. View the radio schedule on www.bom.gov.au/marine</text><text type="postamble">Check the latest Coastal Waters Forecasts for information on wind, wave and weather conditions for neighbouring coastal zones.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="VIC_MW002" description="Central Coast: Cape Otway to Wilsons Promontory" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><warning-summary type="marine_forecast" index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z">Strong Wind Warning for Saturday for Central Coast</warning-summary><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 20 to 25 knots, reaching up to 30 knots in the far east early in the morning. Winds easing 10 to 15 knots in the afternoon, tending southeasterly below 10 knots in the east in the evening. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots becoming easterly 15 to 20 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres around midday. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres in the west. Swell: Southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres in the far west. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="VIC_MW003" description="Central Gippsland Coast: Wilsons Promontory to Lakes Entrance" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><warning-summary type="marine_forecast" index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z">Strong Wind Warning for Saturday for Central Gippsland Coast</warning-summary><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 25 knots, reaching up to 30 knots offshore early in the morning. Winds easing to south to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots later in the afternoon, then becoming variable below 10 knots later in the evening. Seas: 2 to 3 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the afternoon. Swell: Southeast to southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres in the east during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly about 10 knots increasing to 10 to 15 knots in the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to around 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southeast to southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres in the east during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: East to southeasterly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="VIC_MW004" description="East Gippsland Coast: Lakes Entrance to 60nm east of Gabo Island" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><warning-summary type="marine_forecast" index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z">Strong Wind Warning for Saturday for East Gippsland Coast</warning-summary><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 20 to 30 knots, increasing to 25 to 33 knots in the far east early in the morning, easing to 20 to 25 knots throughout by late morning. South to southwest winds moderating further to 15 to 20 knots during the afternoon, tending south to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the evening. Seas: 3 to 4 metres, decreasing to 1.5 to 2.5 metres during the morning. Swell: Southerly 2 to 3 metres, increasing to 3 to 4 metres in the east. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing below 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southerly 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: East to southeasterly around 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots decreasing to about 10 knots during the afternoon. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southerly 1 to 2 metres, tending southwesterly below 1 metre during the afternoon. Swell: Southeasterly around 1 metre. Weather: Cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="TAS_MW001" description="Far North West Coast: Sandy Cape to Stanley" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T10:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T23:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 20 knots, reaching up to 25 knots inshore in the late morning and early afternoon. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 40% chance of showers south of King Island, 20% chance elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots south of King Island early in the morning. Winds tending east to southeasterly in the morning then tending south to southeasterly in the early afternoon. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres, decreasing to 1.5 to 2 metres by early evening. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 2 metres south of King Island. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="TAS_MW002" description="Central North Coast: Stanley to Northern Tip of Flinders Island" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 20 knots, reaching up to 25 knots offshore in the morning. Winds becoming variable about 10 knots in the early afternoon then becoming northeast to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots in the late evening. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres, decreasing below 1 metre around midday. Swell: Westerly around 1 metre. Weather: Mostly sunny. 20% chance of a shower offshore early this morning. Near zero chance of rain elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots inshore early in the morning. Winds becoming variable about 10 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: Around 1 metre, decreasing below 1 metre around midday. Swell: Westerly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower offshore, near zero chance elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Westerly below 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="TAS_MW009" description="Banks Strait and Franklin Sound" type="coast" parent-aac="TAS_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T05:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-18T18:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 20 knots turning south to southeasterly during the afternoon and evening. Winds reaching up to 25 knots near Eddystone Point in the evening. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the morning, increasing to 1 to 2 metres near Eddystone Point during the afternoon. Swell: Southeasterly 0.5 to 1.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots about Banks Strait early in the morning. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southeast to southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres about Banks Strait. Swell: East to southeasterly 0.5 to 1.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower at night.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+11:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+11:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T13:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T13:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending east to southeasterly below 10 knots during the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southeasterly around 1 metre. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
