<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?> 
<product version="1.5" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://www.bom.gov.au/schema/v1.5/product.xsd"><amoc><source><sender>Australian Government Bureau of Meteorology</sender><region>Western Australia</region><office>WARO</office><copyright>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/copyright.shtml</copyright><disclaimer>http://www.bom.gov.au/other/disclaimer.shtml</disclaimer></source><identifier>IDW11100</identifier><issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T08:00:00Z</issue-time-utc><issue-time-local tz="WST">2016-03-19T16:00:00+08:00</issue-time-local><sent-time>2016-03-19T08:04:56Z</sent-time><expiry-time>2016-03-20T08:00:00Z</expiry-time><validity-bgn-time-local tz="WST">2016-03-19T00:00:00+08:00</validity-bgn-time-local><validity-end-time-local tz="WST">2016-03-22T23:59:59+08:00</validity-end-time-local><next-routine-issue-time-utc>2016-03-19T20:00:00Z</next-routine-issue-time-utc><next-routine-issue-time-local tz="WST">2016-03-20T04:00:00+08:00</next-routine-issue-time-local><status>O</status><service>WSM</service><sub-service>FCW</sub-service><product-type>F</product-type><phase>NEW</phase></amoc><forecast><area aac="WA_FA001" description="Western Australia" type="region"><forecast-period start-time-local="2016-03-19T16:04:57+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-19T16:04:57+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T08:04:57Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T08:04:57Z"><text type="preamble">Wind gusts can be 40 percent stronger than the averages given here. Wind warnings are issued for today and tomorrow and describe the highest category of wind warning for that day.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW001" description="North Kimberley Coast: WA-NT Border to Kuri Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots decreasing to about 10 knots in the evening. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower east of Kalumburu, near zero chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable about 10 knots in the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 60% chance of showers west of Kalumburu, 30% chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Variable about 10 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny. 30% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW002" description="West Kimberley Coast: Kuri Bay to Wallal" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres south of Broome. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly clear. The chance of a thunderstorm inshore early this evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny. The chance of a thunderstorm north of Cape Leveque.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots decreasing to about 10 knots early in the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre, decreasing below 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny. 40% chance of showers north of Cape Leveque, near zero chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northwest to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable about 10 knots during the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW003" description="Pilbara Coast East: Wallal to Cape Preston" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Westerly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Westerly below 1 metre. Weather: Clear.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Westerly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres west of Port Hedland around midday. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Below 0.5 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northwest to southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the morning. Swell: Westerly below 1 metre. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW004" description="Pilbara Coast West: Cape Preston to North West Cape" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots east of Onslow in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres east of Barrow Island. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres about offshore western waters. Weather: Clear.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: West to southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing below 1 metre during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres about offshore western waters. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower in Exmouth Gulf in the evening. Near zero chance of rain elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, increasing to 1.5 metres east of Barrow Island during the afternoon. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres about offshore western waters. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower west of Onslow in the morning. Near zero chance of rain elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm in the morning.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore east of Barrow Island. Swell: West to southwesterly below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore west of Barrow Island during the afternoon. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW005" description="Ningaloo Coast: North West Cape to Cape Cuvier" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower offshore south of Coral Bay, near zero chance elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots inshore in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres inshore during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers in the morning. The chance of a thunderstorm in the morning.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2.5 metres during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW006" description="Gascoyne Coast: Cape Cuvier to Kalbarri" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore south of Denham. Swell: Southerly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southwesterly 10 to 15 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southwesterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore around midday. Swell: Southerly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm south of Denham in the afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the afternoon or evening. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW007" description="Geraldton Coast: Kalbarri to Jurien Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southwesterly 10 to 15 knots turning southerly in the evening. Winds reaching up to 20 knots offshore south of Geraldton in the late evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower inshore, near zero chance elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 25 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the afternoon. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower north of Geraldton in the afternoon and evening. Near zero chance of rain elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm north of Geraldton in the afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 20 to 30 knots. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW008" description="Lancelin Coast: Jurien Bay to Two Rocks" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 20 knots offshore in the late evening. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 metres, increasing to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southerly 15 to 20 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Weather: Sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots becoming variable about 10 knots before dawn then becoming southerly 15 to 20 knots in the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres offshore during the afternoon. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the afternoon. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 25 knots increasing to 20 to 30 knots during the evening. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW009" description="Perth Coast: Two Rocks to Dawesville" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres offshore. Swell: Southwesterly around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southerly 15 to 20 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday, then tending south to southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres by early evening. Weather: Sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 10 to 15 knots turning east to northeasterly below 10 knots before dawn then tending southerly 15 to 25 knots in the morning. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday, then increasing to 1.5 to 2.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the afternoon. Weather: Mostly sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 20 to 30 knots. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW010" description="Bunbury Geographe Coast: Dawesville to Cape Naturaliste" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: South to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots, reaching up to 25 knots offshore in the late evening. Seas: Below 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 2 metres offshore. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 15 to 20 knots turning south to southwesterly in the late morning then tending south to southeasterly in the evening. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 to 1.5 metres around midday. Weather: Sunny.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeast to southwesterly 15 to 25 knots tending southerly 25 to 30 knots in the late afternoon then decreasing to 20 to 25 knots in the evening. Seas: Around 1 metre, increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the morning, then increasing to 1.5 to 2.5 metres around midday. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres offshore during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 20 to 30 knots. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres offshore. Swell: Southwesterly 1 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres offshore. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW011" description="Leeuwin Coast: Cape Naturaliste to Walpole" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 15 to 20 knots, reaching up to 25 knots offshore in the evening. Seas: 1.5 to 2 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 2 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm east of Cape Leeuwin.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 15 to 20 knots, reaching up to 25 knots offshore north of Cape Leeuwin early in the morning. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres around midday, then increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres by early evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower offshore east of Cape Leeuwin, near zero chance elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northeast to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending southeast to southwesterly early in the morning then tending south to southwesterly 15 to 25 knots in the middle of the day. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres around midday. Swell: Southwesterly 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower east of Cape Leeuwin in the late afternoon and evening. Near zero chance of rain elsewhere.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southeasterly 20 to 30 knots. Seas: 1.5 to 2.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 40% chance of showers.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW012" description="Albany Coast: Walpole to Bremer Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 2 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres during the afternoon, then increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres by early evening. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm east of Albany in the early morning.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northeasterly 15 to 20 knots shifting southwesterly in the late morning then tending southerly in the evening. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning, then increasing to 1 to 1.5 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower in the late afternoon and evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Southerly 15 to 20 knots turning southeasterly during the morning. Seas: 1.5 metres. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 30% chance of a shower.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW013" description="Esperance Coast: Bremer Bay to Israelite Bay" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres east of Hopetoun. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 40% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: East to northeasterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the afternoon. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2.5 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres by early evening. Weather: Cloudy. 50% chance of showers east of Esperance, 30% chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm in the morning.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots tending northeasterly before dawn. Seas: 1 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1 metre during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, increasing to 2 to 3 metres during the morning. Weather: Partly cloudy. 20% chance of a shower east of Esperance, near zero chance elsewhere. The chance of a thunderstorm east of Esperance in the evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: North to northeasterly 10 to 15 knots shifting south to southeasterly 15 to 20 knots during the morning. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres during the morning. Swell: Southwesterly 2.5 to 3 metres. Weather: Cloudy. 40% chance of showers. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area><area aac="WA_MW014" description="Eucla Coast: Israelite Bay to WA-SA Border" type="coast" parent-aac="WA_FA001"><forecast-period index="0" start-time-local="2016-03-19T17:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T09:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1.5 to 2 metres west of Eyre. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. The chance of a thunderstorm west of Eyre.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="1" start-time-local="2016-03-20T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-19T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres, increasing to 1 to 2 metres west of Eyre. Swell: South to southwesterly 2 to 2.5 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 50% chance of showers in the morning and early afternoon. The chance of a thunderstorm in the morning and afternoon.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="2" start-time-local="2016-03-21T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-20T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Easterly 15 to 20 knots. Seas: 1 to 1.5 metres. Swell: South to southwesterly 1.5 to 2 metres, decreasing to 1.5 metres during the morning, then increasing to 1.5 to 2.5 metres around midday. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm in the afternoon and evening.</text></forecast-period><forecast-period index="3" start-time-local="2016-03-22T00:00:00+08:00" end-time-local="2016-03-23T00:00:00+08:00" start-time-utc="2016-03-21T16:00:00Z" end-time-utc="2016-03-22T16:00:00Z"><text type="forecast">Winds: Northeast to southeasterly 10 to 15 knots tending south to southeasterly during the morning. Seas: Around 1 metre. Swell: Southwesterly 2 to 3 metres. Weather: Partly cloudy. 30% chance of a shower. The chance of a thunderstorm.</text></forecast-period></area></forecast></product>
